Guide to the Office of the Provost records, 1944-2011 RG0037
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Office files, 1965-1988; RG0037 Series 1; 40 Linear feet
  - Salary and Wage Accounting Proposal for Restructure, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Public and International Affairs, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - DEP, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    File may contain materials prior to the listed date
  - Computer Center, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Data Processing, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - National Law Center, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Secondary School Honors Programs, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Division of University Students, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Summer Sessions, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Summer Sessions, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - School of Education, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - School of Education, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - School of Education, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - School of Engineering, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - School of Engineering, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - School of Engineering and Applies Sciences, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - College of General Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Government and Business Administration, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Government and Business Administration, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - School of Government and Business Administration, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Graduate School, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Graduate School, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - National Law Center, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Public and International Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Officers' Meetings, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Maryland Council on Higher Education, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Science Center Committees, 06/1963 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Columbia College, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Columbian College, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Columbian College, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Columbian College, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - College of General Studies, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - College of Graduate Studies, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Vice President for Administration Security Force, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Vice President for Policy Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Vice President and Treasurer, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Business Office, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Business Office, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Sponsored Research, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Personnel, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Personnel, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Comptroller, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Comptroller, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Admissions, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Admissions, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Registrar, 1967-1972 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Vice President of Student Affairs, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Vice President of Student Affairs, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Vice President of Student Affairs, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Equal Opportunity Program, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    File may contain materials before the listed date
  - Vice President for Development, 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Vice President for Development, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    File may contain materials prior to listed date
  - Academic Publications, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Staff Benefits, 1970-1971 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Budget Reconciliation Changes, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Budget and Finance Committees, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Columbian College Lab Fees, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Education, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Engineering, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Government and Business Administration, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Arts and Sciences, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Law, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Public and International Affairs, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Division of Continuing Education and Summer Sessions, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Telecommunications, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Medical Center, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Sponsored Research Indirect Costs, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Library, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Physical Plant, 1978-1982 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Smith Center Athletics, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - George Washington USA, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Marvin Center, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Residence Halls, 1979-1982 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises, 1979-1981 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Budget Reconciliation Changes, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Student Affairs, 12/22/1980 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Relations, undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Columbian College and Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Education, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Education, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - General Studies, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Government and Business Administration, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Telecommunications, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Public & International Affairs, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Summer Sessions, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Experimental Programs, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Finance Committee, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Educational Leadership, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Budget Change Information, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Salary Base Reconciliations, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - SRN Information, Notes, etc., 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Control Sheets for Accounts: Physical Plant, Security, and Library, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Budget Memos, 1976-1977 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Summer Sessions, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Budget Changes, 07/01/1977 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Budget Changes, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Budget Change Requests [3/3], 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    #600-19828
  - Budget Change Requests [2/3], 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    #300-599
  - Budget Change Requests [1/3], 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    #1-299
  - Budget Change Requests [3/3], 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    #500-673
  - Budget Change Requests [2/3], 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    #299-499
  - Budget Change Requests [1/3], 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Budget Information, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Budget Report File: Columbian College, 1967-1971 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Budget Data, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Budget Analyses, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Budget Changes, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Expenses, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Allocation Summaries, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - General Expense, 1967-1983 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence, 1967-1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Clinical Practice Plan, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Operating Statements, 1977-1980 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Medical Center Budgets, 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Medical Center Program: Cost Funding Study, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Medical School: Estimated Income and Expenses, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Medical Sciences Fund, 1960-1971 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Medical Center, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Hospital Reports, 07/1970 --03/1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Hospital Reports, 07/01/1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Hospital Budget Data, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Clinic Monthly Statements of Income, 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Enrollment Data, 1970-1981 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Senate Committee on Planning and Budgeting, 1972-1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Budget Reconciliation, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Budget Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Finance Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Administration and General, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Student Services, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Staffing, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Staff Benefits, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Columbian College and Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - School of Education and Human Development, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - School of Engineering and Applies Sciences, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - General Studies, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - School of Government and Business Administration, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Law, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Dean of Summer Sessions, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - School of Public and International Affairs, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Medical Center, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Library, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - M and 0, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Athletics and Smith Center, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Marvin Center, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Residence Halls, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Other Auxiliary, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Student Aid, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Capital Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Budget Preparation, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Enrollment Data, 1980-1981 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Summaries, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Tuition Income, 1974-1981 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Sloan-Exxon Foundation, 1971-1974 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - George Washington USA Budget Explanation, 1971-1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Revenue Bonds: Academic Center, 1978-1985 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Division Budgets [1/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Division Budgets [2/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Division Budgets [3/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Division Budgets [4/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Division Budgets [5/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Division Budgets [6/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Division Budgets [7/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Division Budgets [8/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Division Budgets [9/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Division Budgets [10/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Division Budgets [11/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Division Budgets [12/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Division Budgets [13/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Division Budgets [14/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Division Budgets [15/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Division Budgets [16/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Division Budgets [17/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Division Budgets [18/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Division Budgets [19/19], 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Division Budgets [1/2], 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Division Budgets [2/2], 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Consortium Economic Impact Study, undated (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Coordinated Planning Committee, undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Council of Deans, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Enrollment Planning Committee, undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Chronological Files [1/7], 08/1968 --07/1970 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Chronological Files [2/7], 08/1968 --07/1970 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Chronological Files [3/7], 08/1968 --07/1970 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Chronological Files [4/7], 08/1968 --07/1970 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Chronological Files [5/7], 08/1968 --07/1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Chronological Files [6/7], 08/1968 --07/1970 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Chronological Files [7/7], 08/1968 --07/1970 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Gelman Library, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Gelman Library, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Gelman Library, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [1/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [2/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [3/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [4/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [5/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [6/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [7/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [8/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [9/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [10/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [11/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [12/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [13/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [14/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [15/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [16/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [17/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [18/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [19/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [20/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [21/21], 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Academic Departments Statistical Data, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Registration, 1981-1984 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Division Departmental Teaching Hours, 1972-1980 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [1/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [2/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [3/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [4/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [5/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [6/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [7/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [8/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [9/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [10/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [11/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [12/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [13/13], 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Division Budget Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Teaching Assistants and GTFs, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - General Administration and General Expense, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Staff Benefits, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Division Budget Corrections, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [1/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [2/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [3/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [4/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [5/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [6/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [7/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [8/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [9/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [10/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [11/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [12/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Division Budget Correspondence [13/13], 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Columbian College, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Columbian College, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences: Artificial Intelligence, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences: Northern Virginai Project, 05/1988 --08/1988 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - School of Engineering and Applied Sciences: Technology and Strategic Issues Research, 02/1988 --02/1988 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - School of Education and Human Development: General, 02/1989 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - School of Government and Business Administration, 1988-1989 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - School of Public and International Affairs: General, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - School of Public and International Affairs: Sino-Soviet Studies Institute, 11/1988 --01/1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Thailand Project: Thammasat University, 1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Medical Center: General, 1987-1988 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Medical Center: Alpha I Biomedicals, Inc., 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - National Law Center, 1984-1988 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Institute of Law and Aging, 09/17/1987 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Academic Computing, 1985-1988 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - CAAC: Miscellaneous, 03/1988 --11/1988 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    Original finding aid does not explain the abbreviation
  - Administrative Computing: Disaster Recovery, 09/1987 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Vice President of Administration and Research, 06/1987 --06/1988 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Athletic Department, 01/1987 --02/1989 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Personnel: Faculty Salaries, 1981-1988 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Office of the Provost Salaries, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Student and Academic Support Services, 08/1988 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Telecommunications, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Treasurer's Office: General Correspondence, 1985-1988 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - University Marshal, 1984-1988 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence: On-Campus Meetings, 1989 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Endowed Chairs & Professorships, 1987-1988 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Meltzer Psychological Services Center Department of Psychology, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Memberships, 09/1988 --02/1988 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Sponsored Projects, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - TIAA Retirement, 1984-1988 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Visitors and Guests of the University, 06/1989 --03/1989 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 01/1988 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 02/1988 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 03/1988 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 04/1988 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 05/1988 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 06/1988 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 07/1988 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 08/1988 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 09/1988 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 10/1988 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 11/1988 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 12/1988 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 01/1989 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 02/1989 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Chronological File: WDJ, 03/1989 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Sponsored Projects, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - South African Divertiture, 1985-1986 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Student Affairs, 1983-1986 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Study Abroad Program, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - University Professors, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Women's Athletics, 1984-1986 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Provost: Budget Files, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Governance Committee: Faculty Senate, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Admissions Office, 11/1989 --02/1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, 09/1988 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Budget Committee, 10/1988 --06/1988 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Coordinated Planning Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Council of Deans, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Council on International Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Enrollment Planning Committee, 1983-1988 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Search Committee: President, 1986-1988 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Consortium-Administrative Committee: General, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Consortium: Library Project, 1987-02/1988 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Commission on Equal Opportunity, 1973-1981; RG0037 Series 2; 0.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of materials relating to the Commission on Equal Opportunity. The materials range in date from 1973-81.
- Office files, 1972-1980; RG0037 Series 3; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 5, Box 4, Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of files relating to Commission for Equal Opportunity minutes, correspondence, by-laws, Smith Center, faculty statistics, affirmative action plan. The materials range in date from 1972-80.
  Conditions Governing Access
  This series is closed for 25 years from date of record creation. Please see staff for assistance.
- Division of Extension, 1941-1947; RG0037 Series 4; 0.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of correspondence, lists of students, memos, annual reports, student papers, etc., of the Division of Extension (Sidney Hall, director). The materials range in date from 1941-47.
- Commission for the Year 2000, 1984-1985; RG0037 Series 5; 2 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 4, Box 1, Box 2)
  The Commission for the Year 2000 was charged by President Lloyd Elliott with studying the mission and programs of The George Washington University and with recommending new program directions or emphases to place the University among the leading universities of the world over the next fifteen years. Associate Provost Marianne R. Phelps Chaired the Commission. John G. Boswell, Chair of the Department of Education and Professor of Education, L. Thompson Bowles, Dean of the Medical Center for Academic Affairs and Professor of Surgery, Edward A. Caress Associate Dean of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences and Professor of Chemistry, William R. Johnson, Chair of the Department of History and Associate Professor of History, William H. Marlow, Professor of Operations Research, Robert E. Park, Professor of Law, Susan J. Tolchin, Professor of Public Administration, Harry E. Yeide, Chair of the Department of Religion and Professor of Religion, Roderick S. French, Vice President for Academic Affairs, ex-officio, William D. Johnson, Provost, ex-officio, rounded out the membership of the committee.
  This series consists of correspondence, minutes, agendas, reports. The materials range in date from 1984-85.
  - Correspondence: Appointment to the Commission, minutes, agendas, 01/12/1984 --04/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Summaries of Commission meetings, 04/19/1984 --09/17/1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Questions for Deans and responses
  - ODK Remarks, 11/8/1984 --03/21/1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes from meeting of November 8; Remarks to the Board of Trustees March 21, 1985; Retention/ Attrition Perspective; Management Issues for Commission Deliberation.
  - Programs and Degrees offered from different Schools, 1983 --03/06/1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    General reports: Report of the 1983 Trustee Update Committee, Trend Analysis Program brochure. Custom Computer Research: "Long-Range Planning" March 6, 1984.
  - A Bibliography of Faculty Publications, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Comments on the Commission by Administrators: Michael J. Worth, Vice President for Development; J.Y. Ruth, Communications; Linda Donnels, Assistant Dean Educational Services; William P. Smith, Jr., Vice President for Student Affairs; Carl J. Lange, Vice President for Administration.
  - Opportunities for Minority Students, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Memorandum from William P. Smith, Vice President for Student Affairs. Vice President for Development report, July 5, 1984. "Student Life on Campus," A Report to the President's Commission for the Year 2000.
  - Alumni comments on the Commission, 05/16/1984 --06/18/1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Also includes individual Faculty Members Comments on the Commission. March 29- June 1, 1984.
  - Faculty Members Comments on the Commission, 03/29/1984 --06/01/1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)